Jay James

Full stack Software Engineer

PROFILE

I am a senior full stack software engineer and have over 8 years of experience in web and Mobile app design and development. I have mastered HTML, CSS, JavaScript and its frameworks like as Angular, React/Next, Vue.js/Nuxt.js, TypeScript, React Native, Node, express and have good **e**yes in modern website design.

Fast communication + best quality . Backend Frameworks: WordPress, Laravel, Django

Other skills

services: Amazon WebService, Google Cloud

Tools: Docker, Jira

Language: PHP, JavaScript, Java

Smart Contract, Solidity

HOBBIES

Badminton Ping- Pong reading

EDUCATION

German Jordanian University

9/2011-10/2014

- -Specialized in Computer science
- -Major: Computer programming
- Degree: Master's degree

WORK EXPERIENCE

Eleks(Front end application developer)

2/2015-7/2017

- -Worked for Eleks for 2 years
- -Build web application using React.js and integrated several APIs
- -role: designer, developer
- -salary: \$6000/month

Ambitious people group (JavaScript developer)

9/2018-4/2021

- -worked for 4 years
- -several kinds of software development Tracking solution, Cloud/IoT based Projects
- -Java, Spring Boot, JavaScript, React, TypeScript, AWS, IoT,
- -salary: \$6500 -8000/month

Upwork (Full stack Software Engineer)

7/2021-4/2022

- -Worked as a full stack software engineer for Upwork
- -Main Stack is Front end design and development & API design, dev
- React, Redux, Next.js, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, Java, Spring Boot, Smart Contract, solidity
- -\$40-60/hr

Mvp Project Development(Full stack Software Engineer)

6/2022-12/2023

- -Role Frontend and backend for sports betting site(MVP project).
- -Frontend role in Mobile app development(MVP project)
- -React, Angular, Java, Python, React Native

